https://wicca.org/privacy-policy/

Home
Where do I start?
Home
Where do I start?
HomePrivacy Policy
This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their ‘Personally identifiable information’ (PII) is being used online. PII, as used in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.
What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website or app?
When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information or other details to help you with your experience.
When do we collect information?
We collect information from you when you place an order, subscribe to a newsletter, fill out a form, Use Live Chat, Open a Support Ticket or enter information on our site.
How do we use your information?
We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:
• To improve our website in order to better serve you.
• To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.
• To quickly process your transactions.
How do we protect visitor information?
Our website is scanned on a regular basis for security holes and known vulnerabilities in order to make your visit to our site as safe as possible.
We use regular Malware Scanning.
Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. In addition, all sensitive/credit information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.
We implement a variety of security measures when a user places an order to maintain the safety of your personal information.
All transactions are processed through a gateway provider and are not stored or processed on our servers.
Do we use 'cookies'?
Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site’s or service provider’s systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.
We use cookies to:
• Help remember and process the items in the shopping cart.
• Understand and save user’s preferences for future visits.
You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser’s Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.
If you disable cookies off, some features will be disabled It won’t affect the user’s experience that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly.
However, you can still place orders .
How does our site handle do not track signals?
We honor do not track signals and do not track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place.
Does our site allow third-party behavioral tracking?
It’s also important to note that we do not allow third-party behavioral tracking
Third Party Disclosure
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information.
Third-party links
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third-party products or services on our website. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.
Google
Google’s advertising requirements can be summed up by Google’s Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. httpss://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en
We use Google AdSense Advertising on our website.
Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on previous visits to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt-out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google Ad and Content Network privacy policy.
We have implemented the following:
• Remarketing with Google AdSense
• Google Display Network Impression Reporting
• Demographics and Interests Reporting
We along with third-party vendors, such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.
Opting out:
Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page. Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising initiative opt out page or permanently using the Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on.
California Online Privacy Protection Act
CalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The law’s reach stretches well beyond California to require a person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting personally identifiable information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals with whom it is being shared, and to comply with this policy. – See more at:https://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpuf
According to CalOPPA we agree to the following:
Users can visit our site anonymously.
Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page or as a minimum on the first significant page after entering our website.
Our Privacy Policy link includes the word ‘Privacy’ and can be easily be found on the page specified above.
Users will be notified of any privacy policy changes:
• On our Privacy Policy Page
Users are able to change their personal information:
• By emailing us
• By calling us
• By logging in to their account
• By chatting with us or sending us a ticket
COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)
When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under 13, the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, the nation’s consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children’s privacy and safety online.
We do not specifically market to children under 13.
Fair Information Practices
The Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information.
In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur:
We will notify the users via email
• Within 7 business days
We also agree to the Individual Redress Principle, which requires that individuals have a right to pursue legally enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or government agencies to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.
CAN SPAM Act
The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.
We collect your email address in order to:
• Send information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.
• Process orders and to send information and updates pertaining to orders.
• We may also send you additional information related to your product and/or service.
• Market to our mailing list or continue to send emails to our clients after the original transaction has occurred.
To be in accordance with CANSPAM we agree to the following:
• NOT use false or misleading subjects or email addresses.
• Identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way.
• Include the physical address of our business or site headquarters.
• Monitor third-party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.
• Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly.
• Allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email.
If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can email us at contact@wiccanew.wpengine.com and we will promptly remove you from ALL correspondence.
School LinksCourses
The Roots of Our Teaching
School FAQ
Quick LinksThe Church
Basic Tenets of Wicca Craft
The Founders of Wicca
A Brief History of Wicca
Church FAQ
Recent Posts
Love Horoscope for the Week of October 5 — Sasstrology.com
Love Horoscope for the Week of September 28 — Sasstrology.com
Love Horoscope for the Week of September 21 — Sasstrology.com
Blog Archive Blog Archive
Select Month
October 2020  (1)
September 2020  (4)
August 2020  (6)
July 2020  (5)
June 2020  (8)
May 2020  (6)
April 2020  (12)
March 2020  (9)
February 2020  (6)
January 2020  (12)
November 2019  (1)
September 2019  (1)
May 2019  (2)
March 2019  (1)
June 2018  (1)
May 2018  (1)
April 2018  (1)
January 2018  (1)
December 2017  (1)
November 2017  (1)
July 2017  (1)
April 2017  (1)
March 2017  (1)
January 2017  (2)
December 2016  (2)
October 2016  (2)
September 2016  (1)
July 2016  (1)
May 2016  (2)
March 2016  (1)
January 2016  (2)
October 2015  (3)
September 2015  (1)
August 2015  (2)
June 2015  (2)
May 2015  (2)
April 2015  (2)
March 2015  (3)
February 2015  (4)
January 2015  (4)
December 2014  (2)
November 2014  (5)
October 2014  (2)
September 2014  (2)
August 2014  (2)
July 2014  (1)
May 2014  (3)
April 2014  (5)
March 2014  (3)
February 2014  (1)
January 2014  (2)
November 2013  (7)
October 2013  (4)
September 2013  (2)
August 2013  (1)
June 2013  (1)
May 2013  (6)
April 2013  (10)
March 2013  (5)
February 2013  (6)
January 2013  (13)
December 2012  (5)
October 2012  (1)
September 2012  (4)
August 2012  (4)
July 2012  (2)
June 2012  (6)
May 2012  (6)
April 2012  (1)
March 2012  (3)
February 2012  (4)
January 2012  (3)
December 2011  (4)
November 2011  (1)
October 2011  (3)
September 2011  (7)
August 2011  (12)
July 2011  (7)
June 2011  (10)
May 2011  (3)
April 2011  (11)
March 2011  (11)
February 2011  (5)
January 2011  (9)
December 2010  (7)
November 2010  (5)
October 2010  (7)
September 2010  (6)
August 2010  (22)
July 2010  (2)
June 2010  (5)
May 2010  (5)
April 2010  (6)
March 2010  (10)
February 2010  (6)
January 2010  (7)
December 2009  (4)
November 2009  (9)
October 2009  (8)
September 2009  (10)
August 2009  (6)
July 2009  (1)
June 2009  (3)
May 2009  (2)
April 2009  (18)
March 2009  (4)
February 2009  (7)
January 2009  (5)
December 2008  (6)
November 2008  (2)
October 2008  (2)
September 2008  (8)
August 2008  (3)
July 2008  (4)
June 2008  (3)
May 2008  (3)
April 2008  (7)
March 2008  (5)
February 2008  (2)
January 2008  (4)
December 2007  (8)
November 2007  (7)
October 2007  (8)
September 2007  (10)
August 2007  (7)
July 2007  (2)
June 2007  (5)
April 2007  (1)
June 2006  (1)
Useful links
Always Positive Paganism
Letter for Parents
Privacy Policy
Refund Policy
Menu
Always Positive Paganism
Letter for Parents
Youtube
Copyright © 2020 The Church and School of Wicca, All Rights Reserved | Site Map | Contact Us | Mail Correspondence Terms | Online Correspondence Terms
